NARRATOR: Previously onWhy Women Kill...
-This must be Mr. Hemple. -The guy whose life you ruined.
You're going to pay for what you did to me, Loomis.
[grunting, groaning]
Don't you touch him!
Hey! Stop.
-Let me see. -Okay. I'm fine.
Rita is coming to my home?
GRACE: With the entire nominating committee.
Surprise inspection.
Ladies.
ALL: Hello.
What a surprise.
I admire women who try to remake themselves.
Does that mean you'll let me be in the club?
CATHERINE: I think you're responsible
for his fall down the stairs.
Once I can prove that, I will destroy you.
A photo of Catherine
in bed with a young buck
would disinherit her.
That scarf looks lovely on you.
I-I'm sorry. Is this person a friend of yours?
I'm his lover.
You cheated on me with that?
What's her name? She humiliated me.
I want to see her punished.
RITA: I think Alma
is absolutely Elysian Park Garden Club material.
MARTHA: I'm falling apart.
Oh, but you don't want to hear how sick I am.
But I do.
I really do.
NARRATOR: Her name was Harriet.
Years earlier, before her illness,
she'd been a schoolteacher.
So it was only natural
she would want to impart one last lesson.
If you live long enough, you will lose someone you love.
Some people f-fall apart when death knocks on their door.
They shed buckets of tears.
Well...
I say it's a waste of water.
Light that candle first.
We should simply thank God
for the time we had with those we cared for.
The ones who gave our life meaning.
Let's have music, too. Hmm?
Something Italian, I think.
[soft music playing]
My point is, I'm not afraid to die.
So don't dwell in grief once I've gone.
I will be finally free of suffering.
That is something to celebrate.
Is the syringe ready, Bertram?
Yes, Mummy.
Good.
Let us begin.
You put the needle in...
where I point.
I would do it myself,
but you know what this disease has done to my hands.
It's a glorious thing you've done tonight.
And always remember that.
Remember...
only the best sons send their mothers to heaven.
♪
NARRATOR: It was not uncommon for Bertram Fillcot
to dream of his mother.
So he wasn't at all surprised to see her that night.
But he was a bit startled to discover...
...that she'd brought company.
[gasps]
Bertram knew instantly why they'd come,
and what they expected of him.
Bertie.
What are you doing up?
I d... I couldn't sleep.
You look pale.
Are you ill?
-No, I... -Hmm.
-I had a dream. -Hmm.
Martha Westcott was in it.
Joan's aunt?
Why dream about her?
We spoke for a long time yesterday,
while you were busy with the ladies from the Garden Club.
ALMA: Hmm.
And she confessed to me that she's seriously ill.
Suffering from cancer.
-No! -Alma,
she practically asked me to kill her.
If you could hear how much she missed her dead husband...
Well, you're not going to arrange the reunion.
Can't we at least discuss it?
You gave me your solemn vow you'd give up your little hobby.
I'm trying to.
But the urge...
-It's returned. -Oh. [scoffs]
I'm just worried if I don't do something to satisfy it soon,
I might have a complete mental breakdown.
Nonsense.
That's all in your head.
Oh. Well, if that's the case,
perhaps I should talk to a psychiatrist.
Have you lost your mind?
That would be the topic of conversation, yes.
Psychiatrists gossip just like everyone else.
The risk is far too great.
Well, I need to do something to rid me of this compulsion.
Bertram, I don't want to discuss this.
Please, can we just go back to bed?
I'm exhausted.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Uh...
I'll be up in a moment.
Operator?
Yes, um...
I'd like the number, please, for a Timothy Keegan.
Um, I believe he now lives in Oxnard.
Yes. Yes, I'll hold.
[giggling]
Yes.
[giggling]: Right.
Oh, thanks, Amy.
You won't be sorry you changed your vote.
She'll be a great addition to our club.
Yes.
I'll see you at lunch.
Oh, 11 votes.
It's almost done.
You're looking evil today.
What are you up to?
Everywhere I turn, lately,
people are trying to humiliate me.
So I've been forced to wreak a little havoc.
Get a bit of revenge.
What do you want revenge for?
You've got a fur coat, a fancy car.
Most people would kill for your life.
I'm looking for sympathy, Isabel, not perspective.
Please, Papa.
You must squeeze the ball.
The doctors say it will help you regain control of your body.
Miss Castillo?
Hello.
Scooter, from the dry cleaners.
CATHARINE: Oh, of course.
It's so nice to see you.
Out for a stroll?
I always bring my Papa here
for his special exercises.
You're a good daughter.
Nothing matters more than family.
That's what my mom used to say,
before she died.
Oh, Papa. You dropped the ball.
I seemed to have got some mustard on my shirt.
You don't happen to have a hankie?
Oh, I think so.
When did you lose your mama?
I was ten.
Oh. So young.
I loved her so much.
We had so much fun.
Well, I... I don't seem to be helping much.
Oh, uh...
Try the water fountain.
SCOOTER: So...
Do you go to the movies?
Oh, yes. I-I love foreign films.
I actually enjoy reading subtitles.
You know, maybe we could...
Oh. What am I saying?
You don't even know me.
Well, I know
you're a very polite young man.
And, uh,
there is an Italian movie I've been dying to see.
[stammers] I believe it starts at 6:30.
I'll pick you up at 6:00.
[giggling]
SCOOTER: Nice to meet you, sir.
Oh, Papa.
You're squeezing so hard.
You must be getting your strength back.
[bicycle bell rings]
-Morning, Mrs. Fillcot. -Hello.
Boy, your garden sure does look lovely.
Oh. [chuckles]
Thank you, Eddie. It truly is my pride and joy.
-I'll bet. -Hmm.
So I got a telegram for you.
A telegram?
For me?
Oh, dear.
[clears throat]
RITA: Congratulations to our new member.
Luncheon reception today at 2:00.
[gasps]
Is it bad news?
-[squeals] -Whoa.
Dee! Bertram!
-Where are you? -In here.
Is everything okay?
Everything's spectacular.
-I've been accepted into the Garden Club. -No.
Telegram just arrived.
Telegram?
Why didn't they just call?
Who cares?
My dream's coming true.
The reception is this afternoon.
I need to find something to wear,
drive into town and get my hair done.
Bertie, where are you? I have news!
Uh, Daddy's gone.
Gone where?
He left you a note.
He took the bus to meet someone down in Oxnard.
He'll be back tomorrow.
I'll grab the car keys, and you can drop me off at work.
Who on Earth does he know in Oxnard?
[door opens]
Bertram Fillcot.
What a sight for sore eyes.
I'm surprised you recognized me.
It's been what? 20 years?
I was thrilled to get your call.
I-I was a bit curious as to what prompted it,
after such a long time.
Yes, well... to be honest, um...
I'm in desperate need of someone to talk to.
Ah.
I had a feeling.
Oh. Hey, Max. You got a phone call.
-Who is it? -Some lady.
Wouldn't give her name,
but she insisted on talking to the owner.
Hello.
So you're sure you're okay?
I went to see Dr. Rice,
and he said it was just a bump on the noggin.
But he's going to run some tests, to be sure.
Good.
So you got plans for tonight?
There's this guy I've been seeing.
I'm hoping he'll take me some place nice.
No such luck.
I think he wants you to come to his apartment tonight.
Does he really?
Not what you think.
I'm going to make you dinner.
Stop the presses. You cook?
Let's just say I know my way around a pork chop.
Oh, and I'm going to be making you tapioca for dessert.
I don't know how, but...
you just got better-looking.
[Dee chuckles]
Ma'am, listen. I don't tolerate my waitresses
being rude to the customers.
I promise, I will handle this.
Now, did you get her name?
No? Well, can you describe her to me?
She was blonde and...
heavyset.
Some might use the word "fat,"
but I don't like to be cruel.
[Dee laughing]
♪
Hello, ladies.
Am I the last one to arrive?
How rude to be late to my own induction.
I-I couldn't decide what to wear.
I knew there would be photos taken, so...
Uh, what is the protocol? Do I...
...make a little speech, like at the Oscars?
Alma, what are you...?
All I really want to say is how happy
and how proud you've made me.
Alma, stop.
What's wrong?
You shouldn't be here.
But...
I was invited. I-I'm the new member.
No, dear.
[stammers] We voted. Um...
Ada Coy was chosen.
I-I received a telegram.
And-and it said "congratulations"
and it said to come here for lunch.
A telegram?
Rita?
Oh, dear.
My maid must have gotten mixed up and...
sent the telegram to you.
Ada and Alma are such similar names.
I am so...
so terribly sorry for the mix-up.
But please, have a drink at the bar,
and some food, if you'd like.
On me, of course.
No, I should go.
RITA: Uh...
♪
[indistinct chatter]
[Dee sighs]
What's going on?
Max just gave me the heave-ho.
Why?
Some customer complained about me.
She told Max I insulted her.
That's ridiculous.
You're nice to everybody.
-It had to have been one of the other girls. -No.
She said it was the fat girl.
And then demanded Max fire me.
Who the hell is this broad?
She wouldn't give Max her name.
But he still believed her, so to hell with him...
and this crummy job.
Is there some lady out there who hates your guts?
Aw, geez.
[exhales sharply]
Would you like a spot of tea before dinner?
Ah. Well, I thought I might provide
a little liquid refreshment.
I remember how much you used to like whiskey.
Bertie, that's very thoughtful, but, um...
I don't drink anymore.
Oh. You don't?
Over the years, I realized I had a problem.
Got so bad, I was sipping communion wine between Masses.
Father.
Took me ages to quit, but I finally did.
Thank the Heavenly Lord.
Well, good for you.
Oh, well.
A cup of tea will be fine.
So, what did you want to talk about?
I know you've retired, um...
Relax.
The seal of the confessional still holds.
Good. Good. Good.
Does your, uh, problem involve that nice wife of yours?
-What was her name? -Alma.
Yes, we've been having some marital difficulties.
She's upset with me.
Well, I'm curious.
Why not discuss this situation with, uh, your parish priest?
Why come so far to see me?
Because you're the only one
who could understand what I've been doing.
And why is that?
Because you're the only one who knows
that I killed my mother.
[glass breaking]
CATHERINE: So...
I get 50 points for using all my letters, and with that...
I win again.
Isn't that amazing?
Hold it. I don't know that word.
Given how you clean this house, I am not surprised.
[doorbell rings]
I'll get it.
Like you have a choice.
Papa, this game is called Scrabble.
It's so much fun.
Once you get better,
we're going to play every night. Hmm?
Boy, you're really giving him something to live for.
Uh... the dry cleaner's here.
At the front door?
Why do we even have a servants' entrance?
Hey, everybody.
CATHERINE: Scooter, right on time.
I'm never late for the movies.
Isabel...
-where did I leave my purse? -I'm not sure.
-[Rita clears throat] -I'll help you find it.
What are you doing?
-Getting ready to seduce Catherine. -Shh.
Not in front of her father.
Getting Catherine in the sack, that's what you wanted, right?
Well, that was before you cheated on me.
Oh, you'll get over it.
Especially once you got photos
of me and Catherine doing naked-naughty things.
[sighs]
How long will it take?
A few days.
Of course, it would be easier
if I had my old apartment back.
On one condition.
No more waitresses.
I promise.
So...
did you miss me?
You know I have.
CATHERINE: I found my purse.
Oh, swell.
Don't worry, Papa.
I'll be back soon.
[Rita chuckling]
Scooter and Miss Catherine?
What the hell is going on?
Oh, something delicious.
Come upstairs, and I'll tell you all about it.
-I'm so sorry about this. -It-it's all right.
I think there's a dustpan under the sink in the kitchen.
-Could you get it for me? -Yes. Yes.
I'll be right back.
YOUNG TIM: Bertram.
Your father says you have a question for me.
Is Mummy going to hell?
Bertie?
Why would you ask such a thing?
Aunt Elsa says that's where she's going
because of how she died.
She should not have said that.
But I won't lie to you.
The Church does consider suicide to be a sin.
But if Mummy didn't kill herself,
she'd go straight to heaven.
Right?
Of course she would.
We should probably go downstairs and join the others.
Come on.
I need to tell you a secret.
BERTRAM: Here we go.
Everything all right, Father?
Uh. Sure.
You must be hungry after such a long ride.
Why don't I make you dinner,
and we can talk then about anything you like.
Okay?
-Mom. -Hmm.
Are you okay?
Yes, dear. Why?
You just seem a little down.
I thought you'd be on cloud nine
after the lunch with your new club.
Not my club. I...
-I didn't get in. -What?
But the telegram?
It was a prank.
A prank?
[scoffs]
Rita deliberately humiliated me today.
I've been sitting here for hours, trying to understand why.
What could I possibly have done to make her hate me?
-Mom. -Hmm?
Is that the woman who runs the Garden Club?
Yes. That's Rita Castillo.
-Do you know her? -Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
What are you going on about?
Mom, what Rita did,
it's not 'cause she hates you.
It's 'cause she hates me.
[crowd chattering]
So, do you like living in L.A., or do you miss Texas?
Well, I-I certainly miss my friends,
and my job in my church.
But right now, my place is here, with Papa.
At least when you do go back,
he'll have his wife to take care of him.
[scoffs] His wife.
She's the reason I'm here.
I don't trust her one bit.
How come?
Well, Rita married him for his money.
And I'm sure she's been cheating on him this whole time.
Oh. Uh...
any idea who with?
No.
But once I find out,
I'll make Rita and her gigolo very sorry.
[chuckles nervously]
Hey.
Do you have time to get some ice cream?
Oh. That would be lovely.
[both chuckling]
Hi. Uh, two, please.
I knew Scooter was having an affair with a married woman,
but I kept seeing him, until I got jealous.
Then I followed him to a restaurant and dumped him.
In front of Rita.
Which felt good at the time,
but I had no idea she was in your club.
And I certainly didn't know that she would take it out on you.
Oh, Mom.
I'm so sorry she's hurt you.
Mom?
Can you say something?
So Rita's cheating on her husband.
Uh... yeah.
With an out-of-work actor.
I'm surprised she'd do such a thing.
But not that I would?
Oh, well, you're not married.
I mean, shame on you and all that,
but we're talking about Rita.
Okay.
It all makes sense now.
Of course she doesn't want me in the club.
Not only does she hate me because I'm your mother,
but she's afraid of what I might know,
what I might say to the other ladies.
You should say something.
Let the whole town know the truth about her.
That she's a horrible, vindictive woman.
No.
No, now is not the time for spite.
If I am to have satisfaction,
I must be forgiving.
You would forgive Rita?
After everything she's done to you?
What does Proverbs say?
"If thy enemy be hungry, give her food to eat.
"If she thirsts, give her water to drink.
"For thou shalt heap hot coals upon her head,
and the Lord will reward thee."
This is why I love the Bible.
SCOOTER: So...
you didn't mention a husband waiting for you back home.
Are you a widow?
No. I never married.
I bet you were asked, though, huh?
Plenty of times.
Yes, I... I was asked.
Turned him down, huh?
Something like that.
Good for you.
It's better to wait for the right guy.
Don't worry.
He'll show up.
Um.
Do I...
I have something on my face?
Just a little bit.
No, no, no.
Let me.
So, uh, are you enjoying your retirement, Father?
Yes. Not to say that I don't miss my parish
and the people in it.
Yeah. Well, everyone adored you.
You were certainly there for me when I needed you the most.
You were a sweet child put in an unimaginable position.
I'm glad I was able to provide some comfort.
I still remember how you calmed me down that awful day.
You said God would understand what I'd done. [chuckles]
I wish He'd explain that to my wife.
You-you told Alma about how you helped your mother?
-Oh, no. -Oh, good.
It's in the past.
Leave it there.
But she did find out about the others I've helped.
Others?
Yes.
Alma isn't moved to help the afflicted.
She doesn't grasp why I need to.
Compassion is always kind.
No matter how it's delivered.
She never had anyone to teach her that.
But luckily, I did.
Did you say "others"?
Well...
I've met so many people like my mother.
Sick. Tormented.
All ready to leave this world behind.
And I've helped them, too.
The same way you helped your mother?
-Yes. -[gasps]
Do you recall what you said to me?
You said, "God will forgive those
who relieve the suffering of others."
I've always remembered that.
I see. [chuckles]
[coughing]
You were saying?
Not only did I get fired,
I had to tell my mom about my fling with Scooter.
I begged her not to tell my dad, but I know she will.
So I think it's safe to say this has been the lousiest day
of my...
I'm pouring my heart out here
and you're grinning like a hyena.
Why?
I was just thinking.
About what?
Well, during the war, me and my buddies
would talk about what it would be like when we got back home.
None of us expected anything fancy.
Just a quiet life with a nice girl.
Then I got hurt, and my girl dumped me.
I felt real sorry for myself.
And I stopped thinking about the future because...
it didn't look bright.
But now I'm here,
with you,
and I don't feel sorry for myself anymore.
Anyway...
that's why I was smiling.
But go on.
Keep telling me about your problems.
Now that I think about it,
I don't really have any.
[doorbell rings]
Hello.
Could you tell Mrs. Castillo Alma Fillcot is here to see her?
I'm sorry. She's busy right now.
Oh, I think she'll want to see me.
Oh, hello.
Mr. Castillo?
We met once.
At a function.
Alma Fillcot.
[clears throat]
I heard you had a nasty stroke.
Is your recovery going well?
[footsteps approach]
-Mrs. Fillcot? -Hmm?
Mrs. Castillo will see you upstairs.
[gasps softly] Um...
It-it was lovely to chat with you.
Okay.
[clears throat] Thank you.
Hello?
RITA: That's Carlo's room.
I'm in my bedroom, in the back.
Oh.
Beautiful dressing room.
What can I do for you, Alma?
I'd like to talk about what happened today.
Oh.
I know you were embarrassed, but, uh...
I already apologized for the mistake.
The "mistake."
[chuckles]
What are you smiling about?
When we spoke in my kitchen the other day,
I felt that we were finally getting to know one another.
I was wrong.
If you truly knew me, you'd know
that you can trust me with your secrets.
What secrets?
To be clear, when we spoke, I knew nothing about you and...
Oh, what is his name?
Scooter.
Dee only told me that story today.
I was sorry to hear how rude she'd been to you.
I did raise her better than that.
As for your friendship with this...
very handsome young actor...
no one will hear a word about it from me.
Friends don't tattle on friends.
But...
I do hope that you'll honor your promise
and get me into the club.
I know that you've already accepted Ada,
but surely the rules can be bent a little bit.
For an extra seat at the table.
For a friend.
[chuckling]
Oh, Alma. [laughs]
How masterful you are.
How cleverly you've cornered me into...
...accepting you.
I detect a note of sarcasm.
You think you can waltz in here
and threaten me in my own home?
I wasn't making threats.
I was offering friendship.
[laughs] I don't want your fucking friendship.
If I were you,
I would think very carefully before speaking to me that way.
[scoffs] You can't touch me, Alma.
I made sure of that.
Why do you think I embarrassed you today at lunch?
I was making sure that if you spread
any gossip about me, people would say,
"Oh, you can't listen to what Alma says about Rita.
She's hated her ever since that humiliating lunch."
[chuckles]
No one will ever believe a word you say about me.
Grace will believe me.
-She'll back me up. -[chuckles]
Oh, Grace won't back you up.
You see, she knows that I know
about the tawdry affair she's been having.
Grace is having an affair?
With who?
Oh, I'm holding on to that little tidbit for security.
But my point is,
Grace won't lift a finger to protect you.
No.
You can't hurt me, Alma.
Oh, but I can hurt you.
And that gob of pudding you call a daughter...
So you did get her fired.
Oh, and I can do so much more.
Think of the rumors I can spread about her.
Oh, and your husband...
With one phone call,
I can destroy his entire practice.
[scoffs]
How horrible you are.
To think I ever admired you.
I don't want your admiration.
Mm-mm.
I want your fear.
And now that I have it,
get the hell out of my house.
-[insects trilling] -[bird calling]
[gasps] Mr. Carlo.
I was listening to the radio, and I fell asleep.
I'm so sorry. Are you okay?
You poor thing.
Let's get you to bed before Miss Catherine gets home.
She will be so angry with me.
-[panting] -[laughing]
Thank you.
Thank you for a wonderful evening.
I haven't laughed like that in a long time.
Uh, maybe we should do it again some night.
Have dinner or something?
[stammers]
Why are you so anxious to spend time with an old lady like me?
Oh, I'm not anxious.
It's just...
you know...
you're nice.
Hmm.
Is that the only reason?
Also...
you're a dame who doesn't know how beautiful she is.
I really dig that.
Call you tomorrow.
Hmm.
A guy who washes dishes.
-Boy, I hit the mother lode. -[chuckles]
I'm just glad we got through a date
that didn't end up at the hospital.
[laughs]
[sighs]
So. Um...
So...
Um...
Thanks for coming over.
It was a real good night.
Does it have to be over?
Meaning what?
Meaning...
I want to see your bedroom.
Oh.
Um...
What's wrong?
I don't think that's a good idea.
Why not?
No. It's not you.
It's me.
Look, I haven't...
I haven't been with somebody since before the war.
Because of...
Yeah.
I'm embarrassed.
What that land mine did to my body...
Vern. No.
It doesn't matter.
Look, I should warn you.
Don't speak.
My chest isn't too bad.
It's mostly my leg and my back and my...
-Shh. -My neck and...
♪
[heavy breathing]
Well, then I helped Ira West die.
Um... he had tuberculosis.
After him was Sue Cork.
She had suffered a stroke.
Um, then I helped...
I don't need to hear about every victim.
Just give me the grand total.
Oh, uh. Right. Hmm.
Twenty-six.
You murdered 26 people?
Sweet Jesus!
I thought you'd understand.
You were so kind to me after I helped my mother.
You were a child!
Six is too young to know right from wrong.
I hoped you'd figure it out by the time you were ten,
let alone 40.
You've got to stop this madness.
Bertram, promise me.
I'm trying, but it's hard.
What's hard?
You get up. You go to work.
You don't kill. You come home.
Do you think I want to feel this way?
Every day I leave my house,
and I see all the people in pain.
On the streets, in cafés.
Their eyes tell me they're tired of living,
that they yearn for death.
To see their suffering, but to do nothing for them?
I can't bear it.
-Uh... -It torments you
the-the way your mother's pain tormented you?
Yes!
That's why you help them?
Yes.
And when you help them, Bertram,
whose torment are you easing?
Theirs or yours?
You think these killings are merciful. They're not.
They're selfish.
You're taking human life to ease your own pain.
So you'll feel better, for a while.
But it never lasts, does it?
No.
I think this is what Alma was talking to me about.
Then listen to her.
God has blessed you with a good woman
who knows the worst of you and loves you anyway.
Heed her counsel, for the rest of your days,
and you can't go wrong.
All right.
So, no more killing?
No. I swear.
How much of that whiskey do you intend on drinking?
How much will keep me from remembering
this conversation tomorrow?
[humming]
[continues humming]
Someone's in a good mood.
Yes.
So, please, don't ruin it by speaking,
or breathing.
ISABEL: Here you are, Mr. Carlo.
Good morning, Papa.
How are you feeling today?
He's been fidgety. I think he wanted to see you.
Please.
He doesn't even know his first name anymore.
Liar.
His mind is fine.
When we do therapy, he obeys commands.
-Right? -He does?
Yes.
He even squeezed a ball the other day in the park.
[straining]
What is it, Papa?
Do you want to say something?
[straining, mumbling]
RITA: He's probably just bored.
Isabel, why don't you take him outside for some fresh air?
[straining]
Oh, look. He's... he's moving his finger.
What?
Do it again, Papa.
I think he's pointing at something.
[mumbling]
Is it the game?
Do you want to play with us?
[scoffs] Don't be ridiculous.
He couldn't possibly...
Is there something on the board?
Oh! Ah.
What the hell is wrong with you?
I must have lost my footing. I don't know.
Isabel, help me clean this mess.
ISABEL: You got it.
-[sobbing] -Oh, Mom.
Please don't cry.
I can't help it.
The way Rita spoke to me was just...
It was so demeaning.
She's a horrible woman.
Thank God you'll never see her again.
Maybe one of the other botanical societies in town will have me.
If word of my humiliation hasn't spread across Los Angeles.
There are lots of clubs
that would be thrilled to have you as a member.
You're so sweet.
We should start our day.
You put the kettle on.
I'll get the morning paper.
[phone ringing]
Uh, if that's your father...
don't mention Rita.
I can't handle him telling me "I told you so."
Not yet, anyway.
-Hello? -MAN: Dee?
Good morning. It's Dr. Rice.
Oh. Hi, Doc.
The bump on my head is feeling a lot better.
Oh, good. Good. Um...
But actually, I'm calling because of those tests we ran.
We discovered, uh...
This is a bit delicate, but...
Dee, are you aware you're pregnant?
[gasping]
[sniffling]
Oh. [gasps]
NARRATOR: As Alma looked at the ruins of her beloved garden,
she was filled with a profound grief,
unlike any she'd ever known.
And then she saw the card.
RITA: Threaten me again,
and this will be your family.
NARRATOR: And just like that,
her grief was transformed into rage.
For a moment,
Alma wondered how she would go about punishing Rita.
That's when this timid, awkward mouse of a woman remembered...
...she was married to a serial killer.
Captioning sponsored by CBS
Captioned by Media Access Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org